[
    {
     "category": "Categoria 1",
     "question": "Questão 1",
     "answer": "Resposta 1"
    },
    {
     "category": "Categoria 2",
     "question": "Questão 2",
     "answer": "Resposta 2"
    },
    {
     "category": "Categoria 3",
     "question": "Questão 3",
     "answer": "Resposta 3"
    },
    {
     "category": "Categoria 4",
     "question": "Questão 4",
     "answer": "Resposta 4"
    },
    {
     "category": "Categoria 1",
     "question": "Questão 5",
     "answer": "Resposta 5"
    },
    {
     "category": "Categoria 2",
     "question": "Questão 6",
     "answer": "Resposta 6"
    },
    {
     "category": "Categoria 3",
     "question": "Questão 7",
     "answer": "Resposta 7"
    },
    {
     "category": "Categoria 4",
     "question": "Questão 8",
     "answer": "Resposta 8"
    },
    {
     "category": "Categoria 1",
     "question": "Questão 9",
     "answer": "Resposta 9"
    },
    {
     "category": "Categoria 2",
     "question": "Questão 10",
     "answer": "Resposta 10"
    },
    {
     "category": "Categoria 3",
     "question": "Questão 11",
     "answer": "Resposta 11"
    },
    {
     "category": "Categoria 4",
     "question": "Questão 12",
     "answer": "Resposta 12"
    },
    {
     "category": "Categoria 1",
     "question": "Questão 13",
     "answer": "Resposta 13"
    },
    {
     "category": "Categoria 2",
     "question": "Questão 14",
     "answer": "Resposta 14"
    },
    {
     "category": "Categoria 3",
     "question": "Questão 15",
     "answer": "Resposta 15"
    },
    {
     "category": "Categoria 4",
     "question": "Questão 16",
     "answer": "Resposta 16"
    },
    {
     "category": "Categoria 1",
     "question": "Questão 17",
     "answer": "Resposta 17"
    },
    {
     "category": "Categoria 2",
     "question": "Questão 18",
     "answer": "Resposta 18"
    },
    {
     "category": "Categoria 3",
     "question": "Questão 19",
     "answer": "Resposta 19"
    },
    {
     "category": "Categoria 4",
     "question": "Questão 20",
     "answer": "Resposta 20"
    },
    {
     "category": "Categoria 1",
     "question": "Questão 21",
     "answer": "Resposta 21"
    },
    {
     "category": "Categoria 2",
     "question": "Questão 22",
     "answer": "Resposta 22"
    },
    {
     "category": "Categoria 3",
     "question": "Questão 23",
     "answer": "Resposta 23"
    },
    {
     "category": "Categoria 4",
     "question": "Questão 24",
     "answer": "Resposta 24"
    }
]